Warning: No valid end-use efficiency factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default end-use efficiency factor (0.9)
Warning: No valid CHP fraction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default CHP fraction (0.5)
Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (4)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir hydrostatic pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume built-in reservoir hydrostatic pressure correlation
Warning: No valid injectivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injectivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid productivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid production wellhead pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will calculate production wellhead pressure using built-in correlation
Warning: No valid plant outlet pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default plant outlet pressure (100 kPa)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid heat rate provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default heat rate ($0.02/kWh)
Warning: GEOPHIRES calculates pump depth to be deeper than 600 m. Verify reservoir pressure, production well flow rate and production well dimensions

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 23:04
 Calculation Time = 0.005 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Cogeneration Parallel Cycle
 Heat sales considered as extra income
 Power Plant Type = Single-Flash
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 7.97 MWe
 Average Net Heat Production = 70.87 MWth
 LCOE = 2.7 cents/kWh
 Additional average annual revenue from heat sales = 11.2 M$/year
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Annual Percentage Thermal Drawdown Model
 Annual Thermal Drawdown = 1.500 %/year
 Number of Production Wells = 4
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 1
 Well Depth = 4000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 295.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 281.8░C
 Average Production Temperature = 259.3░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 222.6░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 281.4░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 157.48 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 5.8░C
 Average Injection Well Pump Pressure Drop = 6219.3 kPa
 Average Production Well Pump Pressure Drop = 5165.3 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 13.65 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 11.20 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 7.63 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 13.61 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 11.19 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 7.97 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 4.07 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 11.17 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 88.28 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 62.76 GWh
 Maximum Net Heat Production = 79.73 MWth
 Average Net Heat Production = 70.87 MWth
 Minimum Net Heat Production = 56.34 MWth
 Initial Net Heat Production = 79.59 MWth
 Average Annual Heat Production = 558.52 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 3.24 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 110.94 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 41.60 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 53.95 M$
   Exploration Cost = 7.41 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 6.47 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 4.81 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 0.97 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 2.29 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.11 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL      GEOFLUID      PUMP      NET       NET       FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN     TEMPERATURE   POWER     POWER     HEAT      EFFICIENCY
         (-)          (deg C)       (MWe)     (MWe)     (MWth)    (%)
   0      1.0000      281.42        2.4362    11.1739   79.5893   12.6355
   1      0.9992      281.18        2.4895    11.0921   79.4963   12.5576
   2      0.9912      278.95        2.5521    10.7611   78.6159   12.3194
   3      0.9820      276.34        2.6152    10.3876   77.5826   12.0502
   4      0.9721      273.58        2.6776    10.0031   76.4923   11.7696
   5      0.9621      270.74        2.7387     9.6166   75.3723   11.4829
   6      0.9518      267.86        2.7986     9.2318   74.2342   11.1924
   7      0.9415      264.95        2.8572     8.8506   73.0838   10.8991
   8      0.9311      262.02        2.9144     8.4740   71.9247   10.6036
   9      0.9206      259.07        2.9704     8.1028   70.7588   10.3062
  10      0.9101      256.11        3.0251     7.7373   69.5878   10.0069
  11      0.8995      253.13        3.0785     7.3777   68.4126    9.7058
  12      0.8889      250.15        3.1306     7.0243   67.2340    9.4028
  13      0.8783      247.16        3.1815     6.6770   66.0525    9.0978
  14      0.8676      244.16        3.2313     6.3360   64.8685    8.7907
  15      0.8570      241.16        3.2799     6.0012   63.6825    8.4813
  16      0.8463      238.15        3.3273     5.6727   62.4946    8.1695
  17      0.8356      235.14        3.3737     5.3505   61.3051    7.8549
  18      0.8249      232.13        3.4189     5.0344   60.1142    7.5373
  19      0.8141      229.11        3.4632     4.7246   58.9220    7.2165
  20      0.8034      226.09        3.5063     4.4208   57.7286    6.8921
  21      0.7927      223.07        3.5485     4.1231   56.5342    6.5639
  22      1.0009      281.66        3.5897    10.0503   79.6866   11.3510
  23      0.9941      279.76        3.6299     9.7805   78.9362   11.1513
  24      0.9851      277.23        3.6692     9.4391   77.9356   10.9003
  25      0.9755      274.51        3.7076     9.0811   76.8599   10.6336
  26      0.9655      271.69        3.7451     8.7187   75.7481   10.3591
  27      0.9553      268.83        3.7817     8.3568   74.6152   10.0798
  28      0.9450      265.93        3.8175     7.9975   73.4684    9.7970
  29      0.9346      263.00        3.8524     7.6421   72.3119    9.5114
  30      0.9241      260.05        3.8865     7.2913   71.1481    9.2233
