Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (4)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir hydrostatic pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume built-in reservoir hydrostatic pressure correlation
Warning: No valid injectivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injectivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid plant outlet pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default plant outlet pressure (100 kPa)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 22:11
 Calculation Time = 0.005 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Electricity
 Power Plant Type = Single-Flash
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 20.77 MWe
 LCOE = 6.9 cents/kWh
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Annual Percentage Thermal Drawdown Model
 Annual Thermal Drawdown = 1.500 %/year
 Number of Production Wells = 4
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 1
 Well Depth = 4000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 295.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 281.8░C
 Average Production Temperature = 259.3░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 222.6░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 281.4░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 157.48 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 5.8░C
 Average Injection Well Pump Pressure Drop = 6219.3 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 27.30 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 22.41 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 15.26 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 27.22 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 25.67 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 20.77 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 13.62 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 25.58 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 176.57 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 163.65 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 1.64 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 95.96 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 41.60 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 41.76 M$
   Exploration Cost = 7.41 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 3.68 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 4.43 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 0.90 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 1.98 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.11 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL     GEOFLUID       PUMP      NET      FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN    TEMPERATURE    POWER     POWER    EFFICIENCY
         (-)         (deg C)        (MWe)     (MWe)    (%)
   0     1.0000       281.42        1.6379   25.5823   14.4643
   1     0.9992       281.18        1.6379   25.5252   14.4489
   2     0.9912       278.95        1.6379   24.9885   14.3035
   3     0.9820       276.34        1.6379   24.3678   14.1340
   4     0.9721       273.58        1.6379   23.7234   13.9564
   5     0.9621       270.74        1.6379   23.0727   13.7752
   6     0.9518       267.86        1.6379   22.4228   13.5925
   7     0.9415       264.95        1.6379   21.7776   13.4091
   8     0.9311       262.02        1.6379   21.1390   13.2257
   9     0.9206       259.07        1.6379   20.5085   13.0427
  10     0.9101       256.11        1.6379   19.8868   12.8601
  11     0.8995       253.13        1.6379   19.2745   12.6782
  12     0.8889       250.15        1.6379   18.6719   12.4972
  13     0.8783       247.16        1.6379   18.0792   12.3169
  14     0.8676       244.16        1.6379   17.4966   12.1376
  15     0.8570       241.16        1.6379   16.9243   11.9592
  16     0.8463       238.15        1.6379   16.3622   11.7818
  17     0.8356       235.14        1.6379   15.8104   11.6054
  18     0.8249       232.13        1.6379   15.2688   11.4299
  19     0.8141       229.11        1.6379   14.7375   11.2554
  20     0.8034       226.09        1.6379   14.2164   11.0818
  21     0.7927       223.07        1.6379   13.7054   10.9092
  22     1.0009       281.66        1.6379   25.6421   14.4804
  23     0.9941       279.76        1.6379   25.1829   14.3563
  24     0.9851       277.23        1.6379   24.5788   14.1918
  25     0.9755       274.51        1.6379   23.9395   14.0161
  26     0.9655       271.69        1.6379   23.2897   13.8358
  27     0.9553       268.83        1.6379   22.6391   13.6535
  28     0.9450       265.93        1.6379   21.9920   13.4703
  29     0.9346       263.00        1.6379   21.3510   13.2869
  30     0.9241       260.05        1.6379   20.7177   13.1036
