Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (3)
Warning: No valid fracture shape provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture shape (1)
Warning: No valid fracture area provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture area (250,000 m2)
Warning: No valid number of fractures provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default number of fractures (10)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 22:25
 Calculation Time = 1.610 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Electricity
 Power Plant Type = Subcritical ORC
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 3.10 MWe
 LCOE = 35.3 cents/kWh
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Multiple Parallel Fractures Model
 Number of Production Wells = 2
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 1
 Well Depth = 6000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 195.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 185.3░C
 Average Production Temperature = 172.0░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 143.9░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 181.7░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 43.44 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 6.3░C
 Total Average Pressure Drop = 15237.5 kPa
    Average Injection Well Pressure Drop = 2546.0 kPa
    Average Reservoir Pressure Drop = 16581.6 kPa
    Average Production Well Pressure Drop = 662.7 kPa
    Average Buoyancy Pressure Drop = -4552.9 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 6.35 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 5.10 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 2.80 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 5.96 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 4.49 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 3.10 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 0.67 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 4.10 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 40.15 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 24.42 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 2.00 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 84.08 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 47.68 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 18.96 M$
   Exploration Cost = 12.99 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 2.95 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 3.35 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 0.72 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 0.93 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.05 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL     GEOFLUID       PUMP      NET      FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN    TEMPERATURE    POWER     POWER    EFFICIENCY
         (-)         (deg C)        (MWe)     (MWe)    (%)
   0     1.0000       181.73        1.8606    4.1017    8.6219
   1     1.0145       184.37        1.8546    4.3888    9.0123
   2     1.0186       185.12        1.8530    4.4710    9.1219
   3     1.0197       185.31        1.8535    4.4913    9.1482
   4     1.0178       184.96        1.8572    4.4500    9.0912
   5     1.0131       184.12        1.8640    4.3519    8.9566
   6     1.0064       182.89        1.8732    4.2118    8.7622
   7     0.9982       181.41        1.8840    4.0441    8.5259
   8     0.9890       179.74        1.8958    3.8600    8.2613
   9     0.9792       177.95        1.9083    3.6664    7.9767
  10     0.9689       176.08        1.9212    3.4674    7.6771
  11     0.9582       174.13        1.9345    3.2652    7.3648
  12     0.9471       172.12        1.9479    3.0615    7.0410
  13     0.9358       170.06        1.9616    2.8571    6.7064
  14     0.9241       167.94        1.9754    2.6529    6.3615
  15     0.9123       165.79        1.9894    2.4497    6.0067
  16     0.9002       163.59        2.0034    2.2484    5.6423
  17     0.8879       161.36        2.0174    2.0497    5.2689
  18     0.8755       159.11        2.0314    1.8542    4.8869
  19     0.8630       156.84        2.0453    1.6626    4.4966
  20     0.8505       154.56        2.0591    1.4756    4.0985
  21     0.8379       152.27        2.0728    1.2935    3.6927
  22     0.8253       149.98        2.0863    1.1168    3.2795
  23     0.8127       147.69        2.0995    0.9458    2.8591
  24     0.8002       145.42        2.1126    0.7807    2.4313
  25     1.0000       181.73        2.1253    3.8370    8.0655
  26     1.0155       184.55        2.1378    4.1249    8.4573
  27     1.0190       185.18        2.1500    4.1813    8.5260
  28     1.0196       185.29        2.1618    4.1808    8.5173
  29     1.0172       184.85        2.1734    4.1219    8.4291
  30     1.0121       183.94        2.1846    4.0118    8.2699
