Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (3)
Warning: No valid fracture shape provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture shape (1)
Warning: No valid fracture area provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture area (250,000 m2)
Warning: No valid number of fractures provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default number of fractures (10)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir hydrostatic pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume built-in reservoir hydrostatic pressure correlation
Warning: No valid injectivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injectivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid plant outlet pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default plant outlet pressure (100 kPa)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 22:27
 Calculation Time = 1.582 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Electricity
 Power Plant Type = Single-Flash
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 14.34 MWe
 LCOE = 16.9 cents/kWh
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Multiple Parallel Fractures Model
 Number of Production Wells = 4
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 4
 Well Depth = 5000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 265.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 252.0░C
 Average Production Temperature = 228.3░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 198.4░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 249.8░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 133.00 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 2.6░C
 Average Injection Well Pump Pressure Drop = 7974.4 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 20.69 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 16.43 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 11.55 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 20.24 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 18.60 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 14.34 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 9.45 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 18.14 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 129.38 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 112.87 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 2.09 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 112.65 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 58.95 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 38.36 M$
   Exploration Cost = 9.97 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 3.87 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 11.00 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 1.04 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 1.80 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.11 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL     GEOFLUID       PUMP      NET      FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN    TEMPERATURE    POWER     POWER    EFFICIENCY
         (-)         (deg C)        (MWe)     (MWe)    (%)
   0     1.0000       249.79        2.0944   18.1432   11.9649
   1     1.0063       251.37        2.0944   18.4607   12.0651
   2     0.9721       242.82        2.0944   16.7819   11.5270
   3     0.9278       231.76        2.0944   14.7468   10.8434
   4     0.8872       221.61        2.0944   13.0061   10.2255
   5     0.8520       212.81        2.0944   11.5923    9.6958
   6     0.8213       205.16        2.0944   10.4319    9.2382
   7     0.7941       198.36        2.0944    9.4527    8.8327
   8     1.0085       251.90        2.0944   18.5687   12.0990
   9     0.9792       244.60        2.0944   17.1240   11.6384
  10     0.9351       233.57        2.0944   15.0704   10.9547
  11     0.8936       223.21        2.0944   13.2720   10.3221
  12     0.8575       214.19        2.0944   11.8082    9.7785
  13     0.8262       206.37        2.0944   10.6110    9.3103
  14     0.7985       199.44        2.0944    9.6058    8.8974
  15     1.0090       252.04        2.0944   18.5965   12.1077
  16     0.9860       246.30        2.0944   17.4544   11.7451
  17     0.9424       235.41        2.0944   15.4025   11.0678
  18     0.9001       224.84        2.0944   13.5474   10.4213
  19     0.8632       215.61        2.0944   12.0315    9.8633
  20     0.8311       207.60        2.0944   10.7954    9.3840
  21     0.8029       200.55        2.0944    9.7626    8.9632
  22     1.0080       251.78        2.0944   18.5438   12.0912
  23     0.9924       247.88        2.0944   17.7649   11.8446
  24     0.9499       237.27        2.0944   15.7419   11.1823
  25     0.9068       226.52        2.0944   13.8326   10.5231
  26     0.8689       217.05        2.0944   12.2625    9.9503
  27     0.8362       208.86        2.0944   10.9853    9.4592
  28     0.8074       201.67        2.0944    9.9234    9.0300
  29     1.0054       251.13        2.0944   18.4128   12.0500
  30     0.9980       249.29        2.0944   18.0448   11.9337
