Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (4)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir hydrostatic pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume built-in reservoir hydrostatic pressure correlation
Warning: No valid injectivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injectivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid plant outlet pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default plant outlet pressure (100 kPa)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 22:09
 Calculation Time = 0.005 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Electricity
 Power Plant Type = Single-Flash
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 14.72 MWe
 LCOE = 11.2 cents/kWh
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Annual Percentage Thermal Drawdown Model
 Annual Thermal Drawdown = 1.500 %/year
 Number of Production Wells = 4
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 1
 Well Depth = 5000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 265.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 250.5░C
 Average Production Temperature = 230.7░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 197.7░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 249.8░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 135.11 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 6.6░C
 Average Injection Well Pump Pressure Drop = 7974.4 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 20.39 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 16.81 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 11.46 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 20.24 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 18.30 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 14.72 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 9.37 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 18.14 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 132.45 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 115.93 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 2.09 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 112.49 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 58.95 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 38.19 M$
   Exploration Cost = 9.97 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 3.87 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 4.94 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 1.03 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 1.79 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.11 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL     GEOFLUID       PUMP      NET      FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN    TEMPERATURE    POWER     POWER    EFFICIENCY
         (-)         (deg C)        (MWe)     (MWe)    (%)
   0     1.0000       249.79        2.0944   18.1432   11.9649
   1     1.0019       250.26        2.0944   18.2378   11.9949
   2     0.9949       248.52        2.0944   17.8913   11.8849
   3     0.9862       246.35        2.0944   17.4644   11.7483
   4     0.9769       244.02        2.0944   17.0124   11.6022
   5     0.9672       241.60        2.0944   16.5514   11.4514
   6     0.9574       239.14        2.0944   16.0881   11.2981
   7     0.9473       236.64        2.0944   15.6259   11.1433
   8     0.9372       234.11        2.0944   15.1668   10.9876
   9     0.9270       231.57        2.0944   14.7120   10.8314
  10     0.9168       229.01        2.0944   14.2623   10.6748
  11     0.9065       226.44        2.0944   13.8184   10.5181
  12     0.8962       223.85        2.0944   13.3804   10.3613
  13     0.8858       221.27        2.0944   12.9488   10.2045
  14     0.8754       218.67        2.0944   12.5237   10.0478
  15     0.8650       216.07        2.0944   12.1052    9.8912
  16     0.8546       213.46        2.0944   11.6934    9.7346
  17     0.8441       210.85        2.0944   11.2885    9.5781
  18     0.8337       208.24        2.0944   10.8903    9.4217
  19     0.8232       205.62        2.0944   10.4990    9.2653
  20     0.8127       202.99        2.0944   10.1146    9.1089
  21     0.8022       200.37        2.0944    9.7370    8.9525
  22     0.7916       197.74        2.0944    9.3663    8.7959
  23     1.0026       250.44        2.0944   18.2741   12.0063
  24     0.9963       248.85        2.0944   17.9575   11.9060
  25     0.9877       246.73        2.0944   17.5379   11.7719
  26     0.9785       244.41        2.0944   17.0886   11.6269
  27     0.9689       242.01        2.0944   16.6286   11.4768
  28     0.9590       239.55        2.0944   16.1653   11.3238
  29     0.9490       237.05        2.0944   15.7028   11.1692
  30     0.9389       234.53        2.0944   15.2430   11.0136
