Warning: No valid end-use efficiency factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default end-use efficiency factor (0.9)
Warning: No valid CHP fraction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default CHP fraction (0.5)
Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (3)
Warning: No valid fracture shape provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture shape (1)
Warning: No valid fracture area provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture area (250,000 m2)
Warning: No valid number of fractures provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default number of fractures (10)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir hydrostatic pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume built-in reservoir hydrostatic pressure correlation
Warning: No valid injectivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injectivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid productivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid production wellhead pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will calculate production wellhead pressure using built-in correlation
Warning: No valid plant outlet pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default plant outlet pressure (100 kPa)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid heat rate provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default heat rate ($0.02/kWh)
Warning: GEOPHIRES calculates pump depth to be deeper than 600 m. Verify reservoir pressure, production well flow rate and production well dimensions

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 22:49
 Calculation Time = 1.872 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Cogeneration Parallel Cycle
 Heat sales considered as extra income
 Power Plant Type = Single-Flash
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 4.73 MWe
 Average Net Heat Production = 59.85 MWth
 LCOE = 27.6 cents/kWh
 Additional average annual revenue from heat sales = 9.4 M$/year
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Multiple Parallel Fractures Model
 Number of Production Wells = 4
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 4
 Well Depth = 5000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 265.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 252.0░C
 Average Production Temperature = 228.3░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 198.4░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 249.8░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 133.00 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 2.6░C
 Average Injection Well Pump Pressure Drop = 7974.4 kPa
 Average Production Well Pump Pressure Drop = 5055.3 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 10.35 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 8.22 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 5.77 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 10.12 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 8.25 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 4.73 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 1.64 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 8.02 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 64.69 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 37.19 GWh
 Maximum Net Heat Production = 69.12 MWth
 Average Net Heat Production = 59.85 MWth
 Minimum Net Heat Production = 48.16 MWth
 Initial Net Heat Production = 68.24 MWth
 Average Annual Heat Production = 471.49 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 3.49 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 124.95 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 58.95 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 48.04 M$
   Exploration Cost = 9.97 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 6.49 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 11.43 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 1.13 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 2.13 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.11 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL      GEOFLUID      PUMP      NET       NET       FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN     TEMPERATURE   POWER     POWER     HEAT      EFFICIENCY
         (-)          (deg C)       (MWe)     (MWe)     (MWth)    (%)
   0      1.0000      249.79        2.0944     8.0244   68.2365   10.5837
   1      1.0063      251.37        2.0944     8.1832   68.8542   10.6963
   2      0.9721      242.82        2.1389     7.2993   65.5146   10.0273
   3      0.9278      231.76        2.4110     6.0096   61.1992    8.8377
   4      0.8872      221.61        2.6372     4.9131   57.2371    7.7254
   5      0.8520      212.81        2.8177     4.0257   53.8023    6.7341
   6      0.8213      205.16        2.9640     3.2991   50.8148    5.8432
   7      0.7941      198.36        3.0864     2.6872   48.1589    5.0219
   8      1.0085      251.90        3.1919     7.1397   69.0629    9.3041
   9      0.9792      244.60        3.2853     6.3239   66.2102    8.5962
  10      0.9351      233.57        3.3693     5.2131   61.9069    7.5788
  11      0.8936      223.21        3.4457     4.2375   57.8603    6.5913
  12      0.8575      214.19        3.5158     3.4355   54.3406    5.6900
  13      0.8262      206.37        3.5802     2.7725   51.2867    4.8653
  14      0.7985      199.44        3.6396     2.2105   48.5829    4.0950
  15      1.0090      252.04        3.6943     6.6511   69.1164    8.6607
  16      0.9860      246.30        3.7449     6.0295   66.8745    8.1145
  17      0.9424      235.41        3.7916     4.9568   62.6243    7.1237
  18      0.9001      224.84        3.8348     3.9862   58.4987    6.1327
  19      0.8632      215.61        3.8746     3.1883   54.8919    5.2275
  20      0.8311      207.60        3.9115     2.5334   51.7683    4.4044
  21      0.8029      200.55        3.9455     1.9830   49.0139    3.6412
  22      1.0080      251.78        3.9770     6.3421   69.0148    8.2705
  23      0.9924      247.88        4.0061     5.9235   67.4921    7.8989
  24      0.9499      237.27        4.0330     4.8851   63.3485    6.9403
  25      0.9068      226.52        4.0580     3.9055   59.1522    5.9423
  26      0.8689      217.05        4.0810     3.0975   55.4567    5.0268
  27      0.8362      208.86        4.1023     2.4376   52.2601    4.1979
  28      0.8074      201.67        4.1221     1.8868   49.4521    3.4340
  29      1.0054      251.13        4.1404     6.1133   68.7614    8.0015
  30      0.9980      249.29        4.1573     5.9123   68.0438    7.8201
