Warning: No valid end-use efficiency factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default end-use efficiency factor (0.9)
Warning: No valid CHP fraction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default CHP fraction (0.5)
Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (4)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir hydrostatic pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume built-in reservoir hydrostatic pressure correlation
Warning: No valid injectivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injectivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid productivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid production wellhead pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will calculate production wellhead pressure using built-in correlation
Warning: No valid plant outlet pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default plant outlet pressure (100 kPa)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid heat rate provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default heat rate ($0.02/kWh)

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 23:00
 Calculation Time = 0.005 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Cogeneration Parallel Cycle
 Heat sales considered as extra income
 Power Plant Type = Single-Flash
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 5.67 MWe
 Average Net Heat Production = 60.80 MWth
 LCOE = 10.1 cents/kWh
 Additional average annual revenue from heat sales = 9.6 M$/year
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Annual Percentage Thermal Drawdown Model
 Annual Thermal Drawdown = 1.500 %/year
 Number of Production Wells = 4
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 1
 Well Depth = 5000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 265.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 250.5░C
 Average Production Temperature = 230.7░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 197.7░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 249.8░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 135.11 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 6.6░C
 Average Injection Well Pump Pressure Drop = 7974.4 kPa
 Average Production Well Pump Pressure Drop = 2155.6 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 10.20 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 8.41 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 5.73 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 10.12 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 8.10 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 5.67 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 2.63 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 8.02 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 66.22 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 44.64 GWh
 Maximum Net Heat Production = 68.53 MWth
 Average Net Heat Production = 60.80 MWth
 Minimum Net Heat Production = 47.92 MWth
 Initial Net Heat Production = 68.24 MWth
 Average Annual Heat Production = 479.13 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 2.74 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 123.92 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 58.95 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 47.74 M$
   Exploration Cost = 9.97 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 5.76 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 5.36 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 1.12 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 2.13 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.11 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL      GEOFLUID      PUMP      NET       NET       FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN     TEMPERATURE   POWER     POWER     HEAT      EFFICIENCY
         (-)          (deg C)       (MWe)     (MWe)     (MWth)    (%)
   0      1.0000      249.79        2.0944     8.0244   68.2365   10.5837
   1      1.0019      250.26        2.0944     8.0717   68.4213   10.6174
   2      0.9949      248.52        2.0944     7.8984   67.7418   10.4936
   3      0.9862      246.35        2.0944     7.6850   66.8944   10.3394
   4      0.9769      244.02        2.1219     7.4315   65.9842   10.1363
   5      0.9672      241.60        2.1858     7.1371   65.0413    9.8759
   6      0.9574      239.14        2.2487     6.8426   64.0784    9.6107
   7      0.9473      236.64        2.3104     6.5498   63.1020    9.3417
   8      0.9372      234.11        2.3710     6.2596   62.1160    9.0696
   9      0.9270      231.57        2.4304     5.9728   61.1226    8.7946
  10      0.9168      229.01        2.4887     5.6897   60.1235    8.5170
  11      0.9065      226.44        2.5459     5.4105   59.1198    8.2366
  12      0.8962      223.85        2.6019     5.1356   58.1124    7.9536
  13      0.8858      221.27        2.6568     4.8649   57.1017    7.6677
  14      0.8754      218.67        2.7105     4.5985   56.0884    7.3788
  15      0.8650      216.07        2.7633     4.3365   55.0728    7.0868
  16      0.8546      213.46        2.8149     4.0790   54.0551    6.7914
  17      0.8441      210.85        2.8655     3.8259   53.0357    6.4925
  18      0.8337      208.24        2.9151     3.5773   52.0147    6.1897
  19      0.8232      205.62        2.9636     3.3331   50.9923    5.8828
  20      0.8127      202.99        3.0112     3.0933   49.9686    5.5714
  21      0.8022      200.37        3.0578     2.8579   48.9437    5.2553
  22      0.7916      197.74        3.1035     2.6269   47.9178    4.9339
  23      1.0026      250.44        3.1482     7.0361   68.4919    9.2456
  24      0.9963      248.85        3.1920     6.8340   67.8722    9.0620
  25      0.9877      246.73        3.2348     6.5813   67.0413    8.8352
  26      0.9785      244.41        3.2768     6.3147   66.1386    8.5929
  27      0.9689      242.01        3.3179     6.0436   65.2001    8.3423
  28      0.9590      239.55        3.3582     5.7717   64.2399    8.0861
  29      0.9490      237.05        3.3976     5.5010   63.2655    7.8256
  30      0.9389      234.53        3.4362     5.2325   62.2809    7.5614
