Warning: No valid end-use efficiency factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default end-use efficiency factor (0.9)
Warning: No valid CHP fraction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default CHP fraction (0.5)
Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (3)
Warning: No valid fracture shape provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture shape (1)
Warning: No valid fracture area provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture area (250,000 m2)
Warning: No valid number of fractures provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default number of fractures (10)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid heat rate provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default heat rate ($0.02/kWh)

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 22:41
 Calculation Time = 1.999 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Cogeneration Parallel Cycle
 Heat sales considered as extra income
 Power Plant Type = Subcritical ORC
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 0.55 MWe
 Average Net Heat Production = 19.55 MWth
 LCOE = 109.5 cents/kWh
 Additional average annual revenue from heat sales = 3.1 M$/year
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Multiple Parallel Fractures Model
 Number of Production Wells = 2
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 1
 Well Depth = 6000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 195.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 185.3░C
 Average Production Temperature = 172.0░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 143.9░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 181.7░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 43.44 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 6.3░C
 Total Average Pressure Drop = 15237.5 kPa
    Average Injection Well Pressure Drop = 2546.0 kPa
    Average Reservoir Pressure Drop = 16581.6 kPa
    Average Production Well Pressure Drop = 662.7 kPa
    Average Buoyancy Pressure Drop = -4552.9 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 3.17 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 2.55 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 1.40 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 2.98 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 1.32 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 0.55 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = -0.72 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 1.12 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 20.08 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 4.34 GWh
 Maximum Net Heat Production = 22.09 MWth
 Average Net Heat Production = 19.55 MWth
 Minimum Net Heat Production = 14.16 MWth
 Initial Net Heat Production = 21.41 MWth
 Average Annual Heat Production = 154.01 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 2.00 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 82.91 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 47.68 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 17.79 M$
   Exploration Cost = 12.99 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 2.95 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 3.61 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 0.79 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 1.13 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.05 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL      GEOFLUID      PUMP      NET       NET       FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN     TEMPERATURE   POWER     POWER     HEAT      EFFICIENCY
         (-)          (deg C)       (MWe)     (MWe)     (MWth)    (%)
   0      1.0000      181.73        1.8606     1.1205   21.4077    4.7108
   1      1.0145      184.37        1.8546     1.2671   21.9137    5.2039
   2      1.0186      185.12        1.8530     1.3090   22.0561    5.3414
   3      1.0197      185.31        1.8535     1.3189   22.0927    5.3729
   4      1.0178      184.96        1.8572     1.2964   22.0264    5.2970
   5      1.0131      184.12        1.8640     1.2440   21.8649    5.1204
   6      1.0064      182.89        1.8732     1.1693   21.6303    4.8652
   7      0.9982      181.41        1.8840     1.0801   21.3451    4.5541
   8      0.9890      179.74        1.8958     0.9821   21.0260    4.2038
   9      0.9792      177.95        1.9083     0.8790   20.6837    3.8250
  10      0.9689      176.08        1.9212     0.7731   20.3243    3.4233
  11      0.9582      174.13        1.9345     0.6654   19.9512    3.0016
  12      0.9471      172.12        1.9479     0.5568   19.5663    2.5610
  13      0.9358      170.06        1.9616     0.4477   19.1708    2.1019
  14      0.9241      167.94        1.9754     0.3387   18.7659    1.6245
  15      0.9123      165.79        1.9894     0.2302   18.3526    1.1288
  16      0.9002      163.59        2.0034     0.1225   17.9320    0.6149
  17      0.8879      161.36        2.0174     0.0161   17.5053    0.0830
  18      0.8755      159.11        2.0314    -0.0886   17.0739   -0.4670
  19      0.8630      156.84        2.0453    -0.1913   16.6388   -1.0349
  20      0.8505      154.56        2.0591    -0.2918   16.2014   -1.6208
  21      0.8379      152.27        2.0728    -0.3896   15.7627   -2.2247
  22      0.8253      149.98        2.0863    -0.4847   15.3240   -2.8469
  23      0.8127      147.69        2.0995    -0.5769   14.8862   -3.4877
  24      0.8002      145.42        2.1126    -0.6659   14.4502   -4.1475
  25      1.0000      181.73        2.1253     0.8558   21.4077    3.5980
  26      1.0155      184.55        2.1378     0.9935   21.9480    4.0741
  27      1.0190      185.18        2.1500     1.0157   22.0689    4.1420
  28      1.0196      185.29        2.1618     1.0095   22.0889    4.1131
  29      1.0172      184.85        2.1734     0.9743   22.0056    3.9847
  30      1.0121      183.94        2.1846     0.9136   21.8302    3.7667
