Warning: No valid end-use efficiency factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default end-use efficiency factor (0.9)
Warning: No valid CHP fraction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default CHP fraction (0.5)
Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid drawdown parameter found. GEOPHIRES will assume default drawdown parameter (0.5 %/year) for reservoir model 4
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (4)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid heat rate provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default heat rate ($0.02/kWh)

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 22:58
 Calculation Time = 0.006 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Cogeneration Parallel Cycle
 Heat sales considered as extra income
 Power Plant Type = Subcritical ORC
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 0.89 MWe
 Average Net Heat Production = 20.69 MWth
 LCOE = 60.3 cents/kWh
 Additional average annual revenue from heat sales = 3.3 M$/year
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Annual Percentage Thermal Drawdown Model
 Annual Thermal Drawdown = 0.500 %/year
 Number of Production Wells = 2
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 0
 Well Depth = 6000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 195.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 184.0░C
 Average Production Temperature = 178.0░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 170.1░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 181.7░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 45.98 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 7.6░C
 Total Average Pressure Drop = 14566.1 kPa
    Average Injection Well Pressure Drop = 2546.0 kPa
    Average Reservoir Pressure Drop = 16835.6 kPa
    Average Production Well Pressure Drop = 673.4 kPa
    Average Buoyancy Pressure Drop = -5488.9 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 3.10 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 2.79 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 2.41 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 2.98 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 1.24 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 0.89 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 0.45 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 1.12 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 22.03 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 6.99 GWh
 Maximum Net Heat Production = 21.85 MWth
 Average Net Heat Production = 20.69 MWth
 Minimum Net Heat Production = 19.18 MWth
 Initial Net Heat Production = 21.41 MWth
 Average Annual Heat Production = 163.13 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 1.91 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 82.54 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 47.68 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 17.51 M$
   Exploration Cost = 12.99 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 2.85 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 1.96 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 0.79 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 1.12 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.05 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL      GEOFLUID      PUMP      NET       NET       FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN     TEMPERATURE   POWER     POWER     HEAT      EFFICIENCY
         (-)          (deg C)       (MWe)     (MWe)     (MWth)    (%)
   0      1.0000      181.73        1.8606     1.1205   21.4077    4.7108
   1      1.0115      183.82        1.8585     1.2334   21.8078    5.0902
   2      1.0126      184.02        1.8607     1.2418   21.8456    5.1159
   3      1.0116      183.85        1.8638     1.2296   21.8131    5.0734
   4      1.0100      183.54        1.8671     1.2099   21.7546    5.0056
   5      1.0079      183.17        1.8706     1.1864   21.6828    4.9246
   6      1.0056      182.75        1.8742     1.1607   21.6028    4.8355
   7      1.0032      182.30        1.8778     1.1335   21.5175    4.7410
   8      1.0006      181.84        1.8815     1.1053   21.4282    4.6424
   9      0.9979      181.36        1.8852     1.0765   21.3361    4.5407
  10      0.9952      180.87        1.8889     1.0471   21.2418    4.4366
  11      0.9925      180.36        1.8926     1.0174   21.1457    4.3304
  12      0.9897      179.85        1.8963     0.9875   21.0481    4.2226
  13      0.9868      179.34        1.9001     0.9574   20.9494    4.1132
  14      0.9840      178.82        1.9038     0.9272   20.8496    4.0025
  15      0.9811      178.29        1.9075     0.8969   20.7489    3.8905
  16      0.9782      177.76        1.9113     0.8666   20.6475    3.7775
  17      0.9752      177.23        1.9150     0.8363   20.5455    3.6635
  18      0.9723      176.70        1.9188     0.8060   20.4429    3.5486
  19      0.9693      176.16        1.9225     0.7758   20.3398    3.4327
  20      0.9664      175.62        1.9262     0.7456   20.2362    3.3160
  21      0.9634      175.07        1.9299     0.7155   20.1322    3.1985
  22      0.9604      174.53        1.9337     0.6854   20.0279    3.0802
  23      0.9574      173.98        1.9374     0.6555   19.9232    2.9611
  24      0.9543      173.44        1.9411     0.6256   19.8182    2.8412
  25      0.9513      172.89        1.9448     0.5959   19.7129    2.7207
  26      0.9483      172.34        1.9485     0.5663   19.6074    2.5994
  27      0.9453      171.78        1.9521     0.5368   19.5016    2.4774
  28      0.9422      171.23        1.9558     0.5074   19.3956    2.3546
  29      0.9392      170.68        1.9595     0.4782   19.2894    2.2312
  30      0.9361      170.12        1.9632     0.4491   19.1831    2.1070
