Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (3)
Warning: No valid fracture shape provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture shape (1)
Warning: No valid fracture area provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default fracture area (250,000 m2)
Warning: No valid number of fractures provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default number of fractures (10)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir hydrostatic pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume built-in reservoir hydrostatic pressure correlation
Warning: No valid injectivity index provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injectivity index (10 kg/s/bar)
Warning: No valid plant outlet pressure provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default plant outlet pressure (100 kPa)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 22:28
 Calculation Time = 1.838 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Electricity
 Power Plant Type = Single-Flash
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 20.52 MWe
 LCOE = 9.8 cents/kWh
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Multiple Parallel Fractures Model
 Number of Production Wells = 4
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 4
 Well Depth = 4000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 295.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 283.4░C
 Average Production Temperature = 257.9░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 223.5░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 281.4░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 156.19 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 2.2░C
 Average Injection Well Pump Pressure Drop = 6219.3 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 27.69 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 22.16 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 15.42 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 27.22 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 26.05 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 20.52 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 13.78 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 25.58 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 174.61 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 161.70 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 1.64 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 96.16 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 41.60 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 41.96 M$
   Exploration Cost = 7.41 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 3.68 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 8.75 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 0.91 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 1.99 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.11 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL     GEOFLUID       PUMP      NET      FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN    TEMPERATURE    POWER     POWER    EFFICIENCY
         (-)         (deg C)        (MWe)     (MWe)    (%)
   0     1.0000       281.42        1.6379   25.5823   14.4643
   1     1.0031       282.30        1.6379   25.7969   14.5221
   2     0.9656       271.72        1.6379   23.2963   13.8377
   3     0.9189       258.58        1.6379   20.4059   13.0127
   4     0.8766       246.68        1.6379   17.9856   12.2883
   5     0.8402       236.43        1.6379   16.0455   11.6808
   6     0.8086       227.56        1.6379   14.4678   11.1658
   7     1.0043       282.63        1.6379   25.8771   14.5436
   8     0.9937       279.63        1.6379   25.1516   14.3478
   9     0.9499       267.31        1.6379   22.2995   13.5576
  10     0.9041       254.43        1.6379   19.5403   12.7575
  11     0.8638       243.09        1.6379   17.2910   12.0738
  12     0.8292       233.34        1.6379   15.4852   11.5003
  13     0.7990       224.84        1.6379   14.0031   11.0100
  14     1.0069       283.35        1.6379   26.0548   14.5913
  15     0.9805       275.94        1.6379   24.2742   14.1083
  16     0.9342       262.90        1.6379   21.3287   13.2804
  17     0.8900       250.46        1.6379   18.7342   12.5160
  18     0.8517       239.68        1.6379   16.6459   11.8716
  19     0.8187       230.39        1.6379   14.9607   11.3289
  20     1.0000       281.42        1.6379   25.5823   14.4643
  21     1.0031       282.30        1.6379   25.7969   14.5221
  22     0.9656       271.72        1.6379   23.2963   13.8377
  23     0.9189       258.58        1.6379   20.4059   13.0127
  24     0.8766       246.68        1.6379   17.9856   12.2883
  25     0.8402       236.43        1.6379   16.0455   11.6808
  26     0.8086       227.56        1.6379   14.4678   11.1658
  27     1.0043       282.63        1.6379   25.8771   14.5436
  28     0.9937       279.63        1.6379   25.1516   14.3478
  29     0.9499       267.31        1.6379   22.2995   13.5576
  30     0.9041       254.43        1.6379   19.5403   12.7575
