Warning: No valid surface temperature provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default surface temperature (15 deg.C)
Warning: No valid production well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default production well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid injection well diameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection well diameter (8 inch)
Warning: No valid Ramey Production Wellbore Model parameter provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default productino wellbore model (Ramey model active)
Warning: No valid injection wellbore temperature gain provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default injection wellbore temperature gain (0deg.C)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume option provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume option (4)
Warning: No valid reservoir volume provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir volume (1.25E8 m3)
Warning: No valid reservoir heat capacity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir heat capacity (1000 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir density provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir density (2700 J/kg/K)
Warning: No valid reservoir thermal conductivity provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default reservoir thermal conductivity (3 W/m/K)
Warning: No valid inflation rate during construction provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default inflation rate during construction (0)
Warning: No valid well drilling and completion total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in well drilling and completion cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid well drilling cost correlation number provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default well drilling cost correlation (1)
Warning: No valid reservoir stimulation total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in reservoir stimulation cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid field gathering system total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in field gathering system cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid exploration total cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in exploration cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total wellfield O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in wellfield O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid surface plant O&M cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in surface plant O&M cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.
Warning: No valid total water cost or adjustment factor provided. GEOPHIRES will assume default built-in water cost correlation with adjustment factor = 1.

----------------------------
GEOPHIRES Simulation Results
----------------------------

1. Simulation Metadata
----------------------
 GEOPHIRES Version = 2.0
 GEOPHIRES Build Date = 2018-01-02
 Simulation Date = 2022-12-12
 Simulation Time = 21:49
 Calculation Time = 0.007 s

2. Summary of Simulation Results
--------------------------------
 End-Use Option = Electricity
 Power Plant Type = Subcritical ORC
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 2.64 MWe
 LCOE = 40.6 cents/kWh
 Economic Model Used = Standard Levelized Cost Model
 Discount Rate = 7.00%

3. Reservoir Simulation Results
-------------------------------
 Reservoir Model = Annual Percentage Thermal Drawdown Model
 Annual Thermal Drawdown = 1.500 %/year
 Number of Production Wells = 2
 Number of Injection Wells = 1
 Number of Times Redrilling = 1
 Well Depth = 6000.0 m
 Flow Rate per Production Well = 50 kg/s
 Initial Reservoir Temperature = 195.0░C
 Maximum Production Temperature = 182.8░C
 Average Production Temperature = 167.3░C
 Minimum Production Temperature = 143.7░C
 Initial Production Temperature = 181.7░C
 Average Reservoir Heat Extraction = 41.42 MWth
 Production Wellbore Heat Transmission Model = Ramey Model
 Average Production Well Temperature Drop = 6.0░C
 Total Average Pressure Drop = 15385.7 kPa
    Average Injection Well Pressure Drop = 2546.0 kPa
    Average Reservoir Pressure Drop = 16522.7 kPa
    Average Production Well Pressure Drop = 660.2 kPa
    Average Buoyancy Pressure Drop = -4343.2 kPa

4. Surface Equipment Simulation Results
---------------------------------------
 Maximum Total Electricity Generation = 6.07 MWe
 Average Total Electricity Generation = 4.66 MWe
 Minimum Total Electricity Generation = 2.78 MWe
 Initial Total Electricity Generation = 5.96 MWe
 Maximum Net Electricity Generation = 4.21 MWe
 Average Net Electricity Generation = 2.64 MWe
 Minimum Net Electricity Generation = 0.66 MWe
 Initial Net Electricity Generation = 4.10 MWe
 Average Annual Total Electricity Generation = 36.65 GWh
 Average Annual Net Electricity Generation = 20.76 GWh
 Average Pumping Power = 2.02 MWe

5. Capital and O&M Costs
------------------------
 Total Capital Cost = 83.35 M$
   Wellfield Cost = 47.68 M$
   Surface Plant Cost = 18.24 M$
   Exploration Cost = 12.99 M$
   Field Gathering System Cost = 2.94 M$
   Stimulation Cost = 1.51 M$
 Total O&M Cost = 3.31 M$/year
   Wellfield O&M Cost = 0.71 M$/year
   Surface Plant O&M Cost = 0.90 M$/year
   Make-Up Water O&M Cost = 0.05 M$/year

6. Power Generation Profile
---------------------------
  YEAR   THERMAL     GEOFLUID       PUMP      NET      FIRST LAW
         DRAWDOWN    TEMPERATURE    POWER     POWER    EFFICIENCY
         (-)         (deg C)        (MWe)     (MWe)    (%)
   0     1.0000       181.73        1.8606    4.1017    8.6219
   1     1.0054       182.71        1.8663    4.1996    8.7508
   2     1.0003       181.79        1.8763    4.0917    8.5967
   3     0.9931       180.48        1.8871    3.9454    8.3871
   4     0.9852       179.05        1.8981    3.7869    8.1563
   5     0.9769       177.53        1.9092    3.6235    7.9141
   6     0.9683       175.98        1.9203    3.4584    7.6645
   7     0.9596       174.39        1.9314    3.2933    7.4095
   8     0.9508       172.78        1.9425    3.1291    7.1503
   9     0.9418       171.16        1.9535    2.9664    6.8874
  10     0.9328       169.52        1.9644    2.8057    6.6212
  11     0.9238       167.88        1.9753    2.6470    6.3519
  12     0.9147       166.22        1.9861    2.4908    6.0797
  13     0.9055       164.56        1.9968    2.3370    5.8045
  14     0.8963       162.89        2.0075    2.1857    5.5264
  15     0.8871       161.22        2.0180    2.0372    5.2451
  16     0.8779       159.54        2.0285    1.8913    4.9607
  17     0.8686       157.86        2.0389    1.7481    4.6729
  18     0.8594       156.18        2.0492    1.6077    4.3816
  19     0.8501       154.49        2.0594    1.4701    4.0865
  20     0.8408       152.80        2.0696    1.3352    3.7874
  21     0.8315       151.11        2.0796    1.2031    3.4839
  22     0.8222       149.41        2.0896    1.0738    3.1758
  23     0.8128       147.71        2.0994    0.9472    2.8627
  24     0.8035       146.01        2.1092    0.8234    2.5442
  25     0.7941       144.31        2.1188    0.7024    2.2199
  26     1.0051       182.67        2.1284    3.9323    8.1974
  27     1.0033       182.33        2.1379    3.8873    8.1278
  28     0.9969       181.16        2.1473    3.7553    7.9344
  29     0.9892       179.78        2.1566    3.6031    7.7088
  30     0.9811       178.30        2.1657    3.4434    7.4679
